const cards = [
    {
        title: 'Javascript',
        question: 'What is JavaScript?',
        answer:
            'JavaScript is a client-side as well as server side scripting language that can be inserted into HTML pages and is understood by web browsers. JavaScript is also an Object based Programming language',
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7610',
    },
    {
        title: 'Javascript',
        question: 'What are undeclared and undefined variables?',
        answer:
            'Undeclared variables are those that do not exist in a program and are not declared. If the program tries to read the value of an undeclared variable, then a runtime error is encountered. Undefined variables are those that are declared in the program but have not been given any value. If the program tries to read the value of an undefined variable, an undefined value is returned.',
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7610',
    },
    {
        title: 'Javascript',
        question: 'What is === operator?',
        answer:
            '=== is called as strict equality operator which returns true when the two operands are having the same value without any type conversion.',
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7610',
    },
    {
        title: 'Javascript',
        question: 'What are all the looping structures in JavaScript?',
        answer: 'For, While, do-while',
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7610',
    },
    {
        title: 'Random',
        question: 'Random question 1',
        answer: 'Random question 2',
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7611',
    },
    {
        title: 'Halloween',
        question: 'What were originally used as the first Jack-o-Lanterns?',
        answer:
            "Turnips. Originating in Ireland, people would hollow out turnips and place a lump of coal in it as a type of lantern and set it at their door as a guide for poor 'Jack.' Jack, legend has it, tricked the devil and wasn't allowed into heaven or hell, so he was cursed to wander the earth forever in the in-between. The Irish then brought this tradition to America and found that pumpkins were a far better alternative to the turnip, thus instilling an American fall tradition.",
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7612',
    },
    {
        title: 'Halloween',
        question:
            'In what century did the tradition of trick or treating begin?',
        answer:
            "The American tradition of trick or treating dates back to the 1920s but in Europe, as early as the 16th century people were known to go from door to door on Halloween night asking for food, reciting verses, wearing costumes, and warning of curses if they didn't get a warm welcome.",
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7612',
    },
    {
        title: 'Halloween',
        question:
            "In It's the Great Pumpkin, Charlie Brown, who does Linus mistake for the Great Pumpkin?",
        answer:
            "Snoopy. Linus faints after seeing a shadowy figure rise in the pumpkin patch, thinking it's the Great Pumpkin. Instead, it was only Snoopy, which Sally sees and gets mad at Linus for making her miss out on all the Halloween fun to wait in the pumpkin patch.",
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7612',
    },
    {
        title: 'Halloween',
        question:
            'What Halloween radio drama caused a mass panic on October 30, 1938?',
        answer:
            "War of the Worlds. Originally a special Halloween episode of The Mercury Theatre on the Air, it was directed and performed by actor Orson Wells who adapted it from H.G. Wells' original novel. Whether or not it actually cause mass hysteria and panic is up for debate because apparently there weren't that many listeners.",
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7612',
    },
    {
        title: 'Halloween',
        question: 'How many colors of M&Ms are there in a normal bag?',
        answer:
            'Six. The colors in a regular bag of M&Ms are red, orange, yellow, green, blue, and brown. In 1995, consumers were asked to vote on what color they wanted to replace the original tan M&Ms. Blue won and was introduced later that same year.',
        category: '5f99a204d2c09f182dbc7612',
    },
];

module.exports = cards;
